

Dmytro Maksiuta

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Contacts

shutle369@gmail.com +38(063)7765185 https://webart.work/dmaksiuta https://github.com/dmaksiuta

Skills

- HTML / CSS / SCSS
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Angular2+ (14)
- Angular Material, MUI
- Bootstrap / Tailwind CSS
- React (Junior)
- Figma / Zeplin / Sketch
- Adobe Photoshop / XD
- Git / Jira / Trello
- Manual QA (iOS, Android, Web)

Education

Pavlo Tychyna Uman State Pedagogical University

Bachelor's degree, Faculty of Physics, Mathematics and Informatics 2017-2021

Master's degree, Faculty of Physics, Mathematics and Informatics 2021-2022

Languages

English - B2 Ukraininan - Native

Profile

Solution-driven web developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, Angular, React and JavaScript. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.experience, and speed.

Development

Developed over 200 pages by writing lines of code using HTML, CSS, Angular.

Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability, security and specialized scripts.

UX Design

Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface.

Established presentation consistency across Chrome, Safari, Firefox and other common browser interfaces.

Ensured all websites were mobile-friendly.

Problem Solving

Ran debugging tools such as Firebug and Chrome Inspector to eliminate flaws and glitches prior to publishing.

Conducted testing and review of website design for responsiveness, clarity and effectiveness.

Employment

Front-end developer/ QA at Innovation System

2018 - 2020

Meet the most advanced Business Management Platform the tree-care and landscaping industry has ever seen (Angular RxJs HTML CSS)

Front-end developer at PurePlanner

2020 - 2021

App is your source for fitness memberships, workout classes, wellness services, beauty appointments and much more, the App will be available in the coming months.

(Angular RxJs HTML CSS Node.js)

UX/UI Designer/ Front-end developer at KAU inc.

2021 - 2022

The world's biggest social casino to be played for fun, coins or money (Angular RxJs HTML CSS)

Front-end developer at VanityBlocks

May - June 2022

NFT Premium Project. (HTML CSS Javascript)